transitionsabroad.com 2003-12-18

# Transitions Abroad: Privacy Policy

**Transitions Abroad Publishing, Inc.  
Privacy Policy Statement**

This statement discloses the privacy practices for Web sites maintained by **Transitions Abroad Publishing,** including TransitionsAbroad.com [TransitionsAbroad.com](http://www.transitionsabroad.com/) and [WorkingTraveler.com](http://www.workingtraveler.com/). For further information please contact us at [privacy@TransitionsAbroad.com](mailto:privacy@TransitionsAbroad.com).

Since Internet technologies and standards are changing rapidly, these guidelines are subject to change. Changes will be posted to this page as they occur.

**Transitions Abroad Publishing** is not responsible for the content, appropriateness, or privacy policies of Web sites to which we provide links.

What information do we track/collect?

**Cookies:** Transitions Abroad does not currently employ cookies.

**IP Addresses:** Transitions Abroad logs IP addresses of site visitors for troubleshooting purposes only. We do not track individual visitor's behavior or use of the site.

**Information Request:** Site visitors may request a free information package using a fill-in form. This form requires personal/demographic information (name, street address, city, state, zip code, country), and requests additional contact and sourcing information (job title, company name, email address, how you found our site).

**Mailing List Subscription:** Site visitors may register to receive our periodicly mailed email newsletter. Doing so requires submitting your name and email address.

**Services:** We use several forms to allow visitors to submit orders for advertising listings in our publications. These forms may require a visitor's credit card information as well as personal/demographic information (name, street address, city, state, zip code, country), and additional contact and sourcing information (job title, company name, email address).

What do we do with information we track/collect?

**Statistical Analysis and Banner Advertising:** Transitions Abroad performs statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site (for site development purposes) and to inform advertisers how many consumers have seen or "clicked-thru" their advertising banners. In this statistical analyses and banner advertisement targeting, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. Personal information about you as an individual will not be provided to any third party. 

**Email:** Using the email addresses provided through our several fill-in forms, Transitions Abroad periodically sends promotional email to its mailing list subscribers and advertisers about services offered by Transitions Abroad. Transitions Abroad may contact you regarding changes to our site or mailing lists, or to confirm or discuss orders.

**Data Security:** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we work with our site hosting service provider to put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online, including SSL security for credit card submissions. Detailed information about SSL is available from [Netscape](http://home.netscape.com/security/basics/index.html). 

With whom do we share tracked/collected information?

**Transitions Abroad** shares our information, in aggregate form, with advertisers and other partners. We also make our mailing list available to other businesses/individuals offering services or products we believe are likely to be of interest to our visitors, advertisers, and subscribers.

**Corrections, Cancellations and opting-out**

Upon request, Transitions Abroad will a) Remove you and your personal information, from our database, thereby canceling your subscription or advertising; b) Correct personal information that you inform us is incorrect; or c) Permit you to "opt out" of further email contact (excepting notification of major changes to the service) while still allowing subscription or advertising. To request a correction or cancellation, visit [www.TransitionsAbroad.com](http://www.transitionsabroad.com/) or email [privacy@TransitionsAbroad.com](mailto:privacy@TransitionsAbroad.com).
